Guide to the Mary Winters Behm papers, [ca. 1960]-1990.
Behm, Mary Winters papers,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Mary Winters Behm papers, [ca. 1960]-1990.
4460.
Behm, Mary Winters
3 cubic feet.
Correspondence
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Family correspondence and notebook titled "German program study in Austria, summer 1964".
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Family correspondence and notebook titled "German program study in Austria, summer 1964".
SUBJECTS
Names:
Behm, Mary Winters.; Winters family.; Winters family
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Related collections: Winters Family Papers, #3808, and Joan Margaret Winters Papers, #3810.
CONTAINER LIST
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1960-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence Fester Family (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Shirley and Kerry Fester
- Correspondence Behm and Winters Family (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Mary, Fred and Briam Behm, Eunice Winters, Susanna Winters Barlow, John T Andrews and son
- Correspondence Winters Family (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Edward and Mary Wright Winters, Robin Winters, JM Winters, Dottie Winters Mason
- Correspondence, 1960-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Bill and Barb, Dolan Family, Maurer Family, Helene Stern and Joan and Leon Wenzel
- Correspondence, 1960-1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Abbett Family, Judy Alexander, Frederick Ballard, Berg Family, Joan Heller, Correll Nash, Queener Family, Jon and Carol
- Correspondence, 1960-1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Elizabeth Podolske, Billheimer Family, Ellis Family
- Correspondence Robert and Margaret Winters, 1967-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Letters without envelopes, small number separated from the rest are undated
- Correspondence Robert and Margaret Winters, 1967-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence Robert and Margaret Winters, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Correspondence Robert and Margaret Winters, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence Robert and Margaret Winters, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence Robert and Margaret Winters, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence Robert and Margaret Winters, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Robert and Margaret Winters, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence Robert Winters, 1968-1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Correspondence Robert Winters, 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Correspondence Robert Winters, 1997-2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Correspondence Margaret Andrews Winters, 1968-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Correspondence Winters Family, 1960-2011 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Susanna Winters Barlow, Edward Winters, Eunice Winters and Nellie Frost Winters
- Correspondence Robin Winters, 1987-2012 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Winters Family, 1972-2002 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  JM Winters, Dottie Winters Mason
- Correspondence, 1991-2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Brian Behm, John and Mary Andrews
- Notebook, "German program study in Austria", 1964 (Box 3, Folder 9)